[ Music ]
[音乐]
[ Applause and Cheers ]
[掌声和欢呼声]
&gt;&gt; All right.
&gt;&gt; 好的
Let's do this.
我们开始吧
Hi, I'm Paolo, and later on,
大家好 我是 Paolo
I'll be joined by my colleague,
之后我的同事 Tom
Tom here on stage.
也会上台
And we are here today to
我们今天将为大家
introduce you to SF symbols.
介绍 SF Symbols
Symbols play a very important
标志在界面上
role in interfaces.
有着很重要的作用
They are effective at
它们可以有效地
communicating meaning.
传递意义
They can indicate which items
它们可以显示
you have selected.
你选择的项目
They can be used to visually
也可以在视觉上
differentiate one type of
区分不同类型
content from another, and
的内容
symbols appears in -- appear in
标志通过系统
various contexts throughout the
出现在不同的情景中
This creates a sense of
这在用户界面中
familiarity throughout the user
创造了一种熟悉感
Symbols are used in a variety of
标志的使用方法有很多种
ways, and designing symbols
设计标志有一种
comes with an inherent
固有的挑战
challenge, which is pairing them
与 UI 其它的
nicely with the other essential
必须的元素
element of any UI, which is
相匹配 那就是文本
Text is used in a variety of
文本在 UI 的运用中
point sizes in the UI, and so
有不同的磅值
are symbols.
标志也是如此
We use symbols a lot, and so do
我们经常使用标志
you.
你们也是
We want to make your job easier.
我们想要让你们的工作更简单
Now in iOS 13, we redesigned all
在 iOS 13 系统中 我们重新设计了
our symbols.
我们的标志
You'll notice how the symbols
你们会注意到这些标志
have a rounder look, and how
看起来更丰满
generally they are a bit heavier
在粗细方面
in weight, making them more
也显得更粗 看起来更明显
visible.
我们也将其设计得
perfectly match and align with
与文字完美融合
And while we took great care in
虽然我们花费大量精力
redesigning all the symbols in
重新设计这些
the system that you may already
系统中你们已经熟悉的
be familiar with, we are
标志 我们还是很激动地
thrilled to announce that we've
宣布我们已经
extended this list, and designed
拓展了这个名单
many more, which we call SF
并设计了更多
symbols.
我们称之为 SF Symbols
They are a platform-consistent,
它们是由 Apple 开发的
high-quality set designed by
可以在你们的 App 中
Apple for you to use in your
使用的与平台兼容 高质量的
apps.
一个设置
They come in vector form, which
它们是以矢量形式出现的
means they are scalable, and
这意味着它们可缩放
will render great at small and
不论磅值大小都
large point sizes.
展示良好
They come in weights that match
它们的粗细也
our family of system fonts, San
适合我们的系统字体 San Francisco 中
Francisco -- all the weights.
所有的粗度
And there's over 1,000 to choose
这里面有超过 1000 种可以选择
If these are still not enough,
如果这些还不够
you can even customize them and
你甚至可以自定义
create your own.
并创造你自己的标志
Let's look at them in more
我们来详细地
detail.
了解一下
They're designed to work with
它们被设计成与文本匹配
They're specified in typographic
它们的排版大小和文本一样
points, like text.
是指定好的
When symbols appear next to
当标志出现在文本旁时
text, they all sit nicely on the
它们都完美的出现在同一
same baseline.
基线上
When symbols and text are
当标志和文本
positioned vertically, there are
垂直排列时
two most common cases -- whether
有两个最常见的情形
the text supports the symbol, or
文本支撑标志
the symbol supports the text.
或者标志支撑文本
Horizontal alignment ensures
平行排列让
that everything looks great, and
一切看起来都比较好
this is possible thanks to their
这也可能是因为它的留白
which are not necessarily the
它们并不一定是相同的
same, as you can see in the
正如你们在右下角
bottom-right blue rectangle.
蓝色长方形所看到的
Margins are invisible, but
留白是不可见的
they're always considered when
在屏幕上展示元素时
laying out elements on the
却经常会考虑到它们
Let's look at weights.
我们来看看粗细
SF symbols have been carefully
SF Symbols 很仔细地
drawn to look great at different
让其在不同粗度下
weights, from ultra-light to
都显得很美观 不论是超细
black, just like our system
还是黑体 就像我们的
fonts.
系统字体一样
Every weight has been drawn
每个粗度都是手动
manually, and special
画成的 而且
consideration went into each
每一个设计都加入了特殊的考量
Thinner weights have a
较细的粗度有一种
distinctive, beautiful elegance,
独特而美丽的优雅感
while the heavier ones strive to
而粗的更加能彰显
maintain detail and visibility.
细节和清晰度
There is a need for using
当它们与文本相邻时
symbols at different sizes when
即使文本的大小不变
they are next to text, even if
我们也需要使用
the text size doesn't change.
不同大小的标志
This is something that many of
这是我们中很多人
us already do, depending on the
根据标志可能需要
amount of emphasis that the
强调的部分
symbol may need, and how much
以及可用的空间
space is available.
已经做过的工作
So with iOS 13, we turned this
在 iOS 13 中 我们将其
into a system.
转换成了一个系统
We call these scales -- small,
我们用缩放大小来调用它们 --
medium, and large.
小 中 大
It's important to notice here
值得注意的是
that the point size of the
标志的尺寸
symbol is still the same.
还是一样的
It's just the scale that
变化的只是缩放比例
Each scale remains
每一个缩放
weight-matched with the text,
都与文本的粗细是相匹配的
and, mind you, it's not just
提醒大家一句
linearly-scaled, the stroke
这不仅仅是线性缩放
thickness is adjusted to the
笔画的粗细
weight of the text, and the
根据文本的粗细而进行调整
other great benefit is that
其他好处就是
using scales means that
使用缩放意味着
automatically they're optically
它们会自动
vertically-centered to the cap
与大写字母的高度
height.
垂直对齐
This way, vertical layout
因此 标志和文本中间
between symbols and text is
垂直的布局
automatic for all three scales.
对于三种缩放大小来说都是自动的
So where are these scales used,
那么这些缩放应该在哪里使用
and when should you use a
你又应该在何时
particular scale?
使用一个特定的缩放大小呢
Well, here are 3 UI examples.
这里有三个 UI 的例子
They all use 17-point text, but
它们都是 17 磅值的文本
the container for each of these
但是这些标志的边框
symbols have different heights.
拥有不同的高度
So the text is the same size in
所以文本在这三个例子中
all 3, and the symbols are as
都是一样的 标志也是如此
well, but the symbols use a
但是标志使用了一个不同的
different scale in order to best
缩放比例 为了
fit their space.
来最好地适配空间
And in some places, like
在某些如
toolbars, your kit will do the
工具栏的地方 你的工具包
right thing, and will pick the
会做出正确的事情
correct scale for the control
同时也会自动地为控制
automatically.
选择正确的缩放比例
So when we put all this together
当我们把这些都放在一起的时候
-- resizing, scaling, and weight
-- 改变大小 缩放和粗细
-- it means you can use them
-- 这意味着你可以通过
with dynamic type, and
动态类型来使用它们
everything just works.
一切都运行得很好
And of course, symbols can be
当然 标志也可以
localized, too.
本地化
Here's an example of the Voice
这是一个语音备忘录的 App
Memos app, running in English,
用英文运行
and running in Arabic.
也用阿拉伯语运行
Notice how the time control
请注意时间控制
reflect the numeral system of
是如何反应
the locale.
当地的数字系统的
If you're wondering how to make
如果你在想如何
sense of all these symbols,
理解这些标志的意思
well, each symbol has a unique
每个标志都有一个
name,
独特的名称
and most symbols come in
大部分标志
variants that can be outlined or
可以改变轮廓
filled.
或填充
They can be enclosed in a circle
它们可以被圆圈
or a square, and may come with a
或正方形所包围 也可能
standardized system of badges.
会有标准化的标记系统
And we made it convenient for
我们让你们可以更方便地
you to use these symbols.
使用这些标志
First, they are included in the
首先 它们被包含在
San Francisco fonts available
San Francisco 字体中
for download, so you can use
而且可以下载 所以你们可以
them in your design prompts.
在你们的设计提示符中使用
The scales are accessible by
这些缩放大小可以在
open Type Features.
打开类型这个功能中打开
The default scale is medium, and
默认的缩放大小是中等
small and large can be selected
小和大都可以通过
through the Typography panel, or
排版面板或者
application-specific UI.
App 特定的 UI 来选择
And as a reminder, these fonts
做个提醒
are for design only, not for
这些字体只能用于设计
deployment.
不能用于部署
So how do you use these symbols?
那你们如何使用这些标志呢
How do you access them and get
你如何访问它们
them into your designs?
并将其运用到自己的设计中呢
Well, to help you with that, we
为了帮助你们
created a new app, which is
我们开发了一个名字叫做
called SF Symbols, and this is
SF Symbols 的新 App
what it looks like.
这就是它的样子
It will let you browse symbols,
它会通过集合视图的形式
either in a collection view or
或是表格视图的形式
in a table view.
让你浏览标志
It will let you search them by
你可以通过名称搜索
name, and preview them in
也可以预览字体中
different weights that the fonts
不同的粗度
You can download the SF Symbols
你可以从 developer.apple.com/design
app with the new fonts from
下载带有新字体的
developer.apple.com/design, and
SF Symbols App
speaking of design, design
说到设计
resources -- the new design
设计资源 -- 在 developer.apple.com 中
resources on developer.apple.com
新的设计资源
also use symbols.
同样使用标志
They reference them by name, and
它们通过名称来引用
some of the system icons are now
一些系统图标现在
symbols, too.
也是标志
So if you were using some of
如果你要使用这些
these, they will automatically
它们会自动
use the new designs.
使用新设计
Now that we've seen how to
现在我们已经了解了
discover the symbols available
如何寻找有效的标志
to you, let's look at a real
让我们来看一个真实的例子
Here's a spec that you might
这是一个你可能需要
have put together for your app.
为你的 App 装配的一个规范
You can see how before maybe you
你可以看到在这之前
had to do something like this --
你也许需要这样做 --
specify your images, the
明确规定你的图像
rectangular bounds, and explicit
矩形的范围 明确的
pad and insets, and now, symbols
填充和插入 现在
greatly simplify the paradigm.
标志明显地简化了范式
You just have to specify a name,
你只需要指定一个名称
its point size, and alignment,
它的磅值和对齐
maybe its weight and scale if
如果合适的话
appropriate.
也可以是其粗细和缩放大小
So I'm working on this app with
我和 Tom 一起在研发这个 App
Tom, and here the symbol in the
第二行的标志
second row is a bit too generic.
有点太普通了
It's a list of beverages, so I
这是一个饮料的清单
want to replace it with
所以我想把它换成
something more appropriate,
更合适的标志
something that conveys that
让其可以表达
these are tasty, hot beverages.
这些是可口的热饮
So I think I'm going to change
所以我要把它给换了
it, and I want to go for a
我想把它换成茶杯
That teacup looks great.
这个茶杯看起来很好
I'm sure Tom will love it, but
我相信 Tom 也会喜欢的
it's not included in the set of
这并没有包含在
symbols that we provide.
我们提供的标志中
Well, the SF Symbols app lets
SF Symbols App 让你可以
you customize and create your
自定义并创建
own symbols.
你自己的标志
In order for you to do that, you
为了实现这一点
need to start by exporting the
你需要从 App 中
symbol from the app, and symbols
输出标志
can be exported through their
标志也可以通过模板来输出
This is what a template looks
这就是模板的样子
It has all the weights, and all
这拥有标志所有的粗度和
the scales for the symbol.
所有的大小
The template is in SVG format,
这个模板是 SVG 格式的
which means it can be edited by
这意味着它可以被
most design tools.
大多数设计工具所编辑
It's specially constructed to be
它被专门设计成
navigable and usable through any
在任何设计阶段
of the design stage, and the
都有导向性且可使用
very same template is also
相同的模板也同样
directly used by Xcode as a
作为源构件
source artifact.
直接运用在 Xcode 中
No more tens of hundreds of
再也不会有成千上万的
files floating around.
文件四处浮动
So let's look at how we did our
那接下来就让我们看看我们是如何制作
teacup.
茶杯标志的
First, we went to the SF Symbols
首先 我们来到 SF Symbols App
app, and we looked for a good
我们先寻找一个好的起点
Our teacup is enclosed in a
我们的茶杯被一个圆圈
circle, so I think the circle is
所包围 所以我觉得
a great starting point.
圆圈是一个很好的起点
And so, I searched for circle,
所以我检索圆圈
and it's there.
找到了
So I can select it and export
我可以选择它
its template from the File menu.
并从文件菜单导出样式
I can save it, and now it's
我可以保存它
ready to be customized.
现在就可以自定义了
I can open it in my editor and
在我的编辑器中打开
notice here how the layers have
请注意这些图层都有
unique names.
不同的名称
These names are important.
这些名称很重要
They help identify each
它们可以识别
individual configuration of the
标志的每个个性化配置
symbol, the weight, and their
粗细 缩放大小
scale, so you've got to be
所以在你画画
careful when you're drawing to
来保证你的轮廓
make sure that your outlines are
是在合适的那一层时
actually inside the appropriate
需要非常仔细
layer.
现在我要开始我的自定义工作了
work, and I put my teacup inside
我把茶杯标志
the regular at the medium scale.
放在中等大小的常规层
I make sure that it's centered,
我要保证它居中
and optically balanced, and then
同时光学上是平衡的
I scale it down, just for stroke
然后我把它缩小
thicknesses, and I put it in the
为了笔画粗细
small regular scale.
我将它设为小的常规大小
And then I repeat the process,
接着我重复这个过程
and I scale it up just for
我放大它的粗度
thickness, center it, make sure
将其居中 保证它
it's looking good for a large
在大的常规大小中也很好看
regular scale, and so forth
然后继续直到
until the template is complete.
这个样式完成
At this point, I'm ready to
现在 我已经准备好
export the SVG from the design
将 SVG 从设计工具中导出
tool.
我可以把接下来的事情交给 Tom
I'm sure he'll take great care
我相信他会很好地完成
In fact, he doesn't have to do
实际上 他不需要做太多
It's ready to be dropped in
它已经准备好按照原本的样子
Xcode as-is.
被拖入 Xcode
So if you want -- don't want to
所以如果你不想要
provide all the weights for your
为你的标志提供
symbol, you have to provide
所有的粗度 你至少得
regular at medium scale at
在中等大小中提供常规号
least, then the scales for
然后是常规号的大小
Then same bold for the bold text
然后是针对粗体文本相同的粗体
feature, and if you want to
如果你想要支撑
support all dynamic-type styles,
所有的动态类型
then include medium and bold as
那也可以包含中等和粗体
Of course, you should take into
当然 如果你想要
consideration the typographic
考虑你 App 的
palette of your app.
排版调色
You may need thinner or heavier
你可能会需要更细或更粗的粗度
So to recap, we got to know a
简要概述一下
new library of symbols that
我们需要了解一个
match San Francisco.
与 San Francisco 匹配的新标志库
They are vector-based and come
它们是矢量图
in different weights and scales.
拥有不同的粗度和大小
You can browse them through the
你可以通过 SF Symbols App
SF Symbols app.
浏览它们
We saw how to use them in your
我们看过了如何在
specs, referenced them by name,
你们的规格中使用它们 如何通过名字检索
and how to specify their
如何指定它们的
positioning, and finally, you
位置 最后就是
can customize symbols using the
你们可以使用从 SF Symbols App 导出的
SVG template exported from the
SVG 样板来
SF Symbols app.
自定义标志
Now, I'd like to invite Tom to
现在 我想邀请 Tom
the stage, so he can tell you
来到台上 他会告诉你们
all about how to use these
如何在代码中
symbols in code.
使用这些标志
[ Applause ]
[掌声]
&gt;&gt; Thank you, Paolo.
&gt;&gt; 谢谢 Paolo
Well, I'm really excited, and
我真的很激动
the first thing I would want to
我想做的第一件事就是
do is see if I can use one of
看看能否在我自己的 App 中
these symbols in my own apps.
使用这些标志
And I have this simple slideshow
这是一个简单的幻灯片 App
app, and it has some UI that
它有一些 UI
allows you to change the speed.
可以让你改变速度
But I'm really not very happy
但我真的不太喜欢
with these images.
这些图片
They're very basic, so let's see
它们非常基础 我们来看一看
-- they're a good candidate for
它们很适合被替换
changing, and let's see what it
我们来看一下如果在
does if we have a symbol in the
Symbols App 中
Symbols app.
找一个标志会怎么样
So let's fire up SF Symbols, and
首先启动 SF Symbols
search for tortoise, because
搜索乌龟
maybe we can use the classic
因为我们可以使用这个
[inaudible] style tortoise and
典型的乌龟和兔子
Turns out, there is one, so I
出来了 这里有一个
can use this.
我可以用这个
That's great.
这很不错
And the hare is there, too.
兔子也在这
Perfect. Now, how do I use them?
完美 接下来 我要如何使用它们呢
It's very simple.
非常简单
We're introducing new API called
我们要介绍一个名为 UIImage(systemName 的
UIImage(systemName that works
新的 API
very similar to the existing
它和现有的 API 非常相似
You just pass in the name you
你只需要放入
copy from the SF Symbols app,
你从 SF Symbols App 复制的名称
and that's it.
这样就可以了
If we build and run -- wow, bam,
如果我们构建并运行 -- 哇 砰
that looks amazing, and it was
看起来非常好
just two lines of code.
这只是两行代码
Perfect. Now, Paolo sent me a
完美 Paolo 发给了我一个规范
spec, because we're working
因为我们一起在开发
together on this app, and he
这个 App
really has to stop putting hot
他真的不能再把
Belgian chocolate there, because
热比利时巧克力放在那了
now I really feel like hot
因为我现在感觉自己就是
Belgian chocolate.
热比利时巧克力
But he gave me this spec, and it
但是他给了我这个规范
looks very different than the
这看起来和之前的
one that I got before.
不太一样
It's -- there's less
这里信息更少
I like that.
我喜欢这个
That's less work for me, but
这减轻了我的工作量
let's focus on this image,
不过让我们集中注意力在图片上
because there's a new teacup
因为这里有一个新的茶杯
there.
他还给了我一个文件
teacup.svg file that I need to
我需要把这个 teacup.svg 文件
import into my asset catalog.
导入到我的资源目录
Well, it's definitely a teacup.
这当然是一个茶杯
There's a lot of them.
还有很多
He really put some effort into
他真的花了很多精力
it, and that's what I like about
这就是我喜欢 Paolo 的原因
Paolo.
他非常注意细节
So now, my image is there, and I
现在我们可以看到我的图片在这里
can just use UIImage(named to
我只需要使用 UIImage(named
get to my teacup.
来获得我的茶杯标志
If we run this, I get this.
如果我们运行这个 得到的是这个
This is a real nice and sharp
这真是一个又好看又清楚的茶杯
teacup, exactly what I wanted,
这就是我想要的
but I'm not sure if you have
但是我不知道你们是否注意到
noticed, when I imported the
当我导入这个文件时
file, there are now two teacups
在我的资源目录中
in my asset catalog.
有两个茶杯
It turns out you can now have
你可以有两张
two images with the same name,
有着相同名称的图片
but they are -- have a different
但是它们的类型不同
So let's step back for a moment
让我们回头看一看
and explain what's happening.
解释一下正在发生的事
We're going to use envelope,
我们要使用信封
because the teacup is not a good
因为茶杯不是一个很好的例子
Up until now, UIImage(named was
到现在为止 UIImage(named
pretty straightforward.
还是很简单的
You have an image in your asset
在资源库中有一个图像
catalog, and you can get it out
你可以使用 API
using the API.
将其导出
Now, with symbols, it becomes
而标志的情况
more complicated.
相对于复杂一些
You can actually have an image
事实上你可以拥有一个
with the same name, and there
有相同名称的图片
might be three versions of it.
但是它可能有三个版本
You might have a system symbol
你可能会有一个
with this name.
有这个名称的系统标志
You might have a custom symbol
还有一个有这个名称的
with the name, and your old
自定义标志
non-symbol image might still be
你之前的非标志图片也
there.
依然存在
For system images, there's no
对于系统图片来说
problem.
这一点问题都没有
They're in a separate name
因为它们有单独的 API
space, because there's a
所以它们在不同的
separate API for them.
名称空间内
And so they are -- there's no
所以它们之间
conflict there.
没有冲突
It also means you can never get
这也意味着使用这个 API
a custom symbol using this API,
不能获得一个自定义标志
and you can never get a system
你也不能使用 UIImage(named API
symbol using the UIImage(named
来获得一个
API.
系统标志
They are totally separate.
它们是完全分开的
For custom symbols, it's a
对于自定义标志
little bit different.
这是不同的
We prioritize things now, so
我们可以加载优先级
we'll first look for a symbol
所以我们会先寻找一个
image.
标志图片
And if we can find one, we will
如果我们找到了一个
return that, and otherwise,
我们就会返回另一个
we'll look for a non-symbol
不然我们就会寻找非标志图像
image, and then you get that
然后你们就会得到
back.
那个图像
Now, you might say, "Well,
现在 你可能会说
that's really annoying, because
这真麻烦
what if I want both?"
如果我两个都想要怎么办
But there's a good story for
好消息就是
With the same line of code, I
运用相同的代码
can run my app on iOS 12 or
我可以在 iOS 12 或者早期系统
earlier, and I get the old
运行我的 App
image, the bitmap image in this
我将获得旧的图像 在这个例子中
case.
就是点阵图
And if I run my app on iOS 13 or
如果我在 iOS 13 或以上的系统运行我的 App
later, I get the symbol image.
我将获得标志图像
So I don't have to write any
所以我不需要编写
version-checking code to get a
任何版本检测代码
different image for the
来为不同的 OS 系统
different OSs.
获取不同的图像
Just provide 2 images with the
只需要提供相同名称的两个图像
same name, and it works out of
它就可以立刻使用
If you do want to use the old
如果你想要在 iOS 13 或以上的系统
image on iOS 13 or later, you
使用老的图片
have to duplicate or rename it.
你需要复制或重命名
So let's -- going back to our
让我们回到我们的幻灯片
slides, and one other thing that
我们还需要说的一件事
we have is the configuration on
就是这个茶杯的配置
It should be large.
它应该是大的
How do we do this?
如何做到呢
We create a new type that we
我们创建了一个引进的新的类型
introduced, SymbolConfiguration,
SymbolConfiguration
and we create one with a large
我们将它创建为
scale.
大尺寸的
The other configuration
其它对象上的
properties that are on the
配置属性是
object are unspecified.
未指定的
We only have a large scale here,
这里只有大缩放比例
and then we can use the
然后我们可以使用
imageView to display our image.
imageView 来展示我们的图像
There's a new property on
在 UIImageView 上
UIImageView called
有一个名为 preferredSymbolConfiguration
preferredSymbolConfiguration
新的 UIImageView
that will tell the imageView to
它将指示 imageView
use this configuration to render
使用这些配置
a symbol image.
来呈现一个标志图像
It will have no effect on
它对于非标志图像
non-symbol images.
是没有影响的
If we run this, what a
如果我们运行这个
difference a scale makes.
看看缩放大小的变化带来的改变
Now, you can also use this
现在 你还可以使用
configuration to change the size
这个配置来改变
of a symbol.
标志的尺大小
You specify a point size, and
你指定一个磅值
optionally, a weight or a scale.
也可以是粗度或缩放大小
Now, an important point here is
重要的一点是
that symbol point sizes are not
标志的磅值
screen point sizes.
不是屏幕的磅值
Symbol point sizes are expressed
标志的磅值是
as font point sizes.
字体的大小
They're typographical in nature.
它们本身是排版的
The screen point sizes describe
屏幕磅值可以描述
the dimension of the image, the
图片的尺寸
width and the height.
它的宽度和高度
Now, a picture says 1,000 words,
一图抵千言
so let's see that and visualize
我们来直观地看一下
this.
比如说 在 “Favorite” 文本旁的
symbol next to the "Favorite"
圆形标志
specified using the system font
它们都被指定使用
at 28 points.
28 磅值的系统字体
Now, you might expect this image
你可能会希望这个图片是
to be 28 x 28 points.
28 x 28 的尺寸
Well, it turns out, it isn't,
但结果并不是
and these values are the actual
这些数值
correct values for this symbol
才是这个标志
at this configuration.
在这个配置下的正确数值
And the image is not even
图片不是方形的
square, and it's a circle.
而是圆形的
So for symbols, you have to let
你需要放弃
go of describing the image using
使用尺寸来
a dimension.
描述标志
You have to use the symbol
你必须使用
points, and you can think of it
标志的磅值
as a piece of text.
而且你可以将其视为一个文本
Because if you have a piece of
因为如果你有一个文本
text, you describe it using the
你会使用字体大小来
font point size, and not using
描述它 而不是使用尺寸
It's the same.
这也是一样
Another way to configure a
另外一个配置标志的
symbol is using a text style,
方法就是使用文本风格
and that means that the symbol
这就意味着
will behave according to the
标志会根据
dynamic text style rules.
动态文本风格规则运转
It will behave the same as a
它会和拥有文本风格的
piece of text with the text
文本一样运转
So it matches great with text
它与文本风格匹配得
styles.
非常好
And imageView will automatically
imageView 会自动地
change the size of the image,
改变图像的尺寸
and look up the right size at
还会在运行的时候
run time, depending on the
根据 App 的
preferred content size category
偏好内容尺寸目录
of the app.
来查找正确的尺寸
You can see this in practice.
在实际操作中你会看到
Like, the text is nice and
比如这个文本很好看
large, and the symbols scaled
字体也很大 那么标志也
accordingly.
随之缩放
And they have the nice -- the
它们拥有非常好看的
same weight.
相同的粗度
So images can change size
所以图片可以
dynamically, and we have to talk
动态地改变大小 我们必须要谈到这个
about this, because you usually
因为你一般都会想要
want to constrain an image by
通过宽度和高度
width and height.
压缩一个图片
And since a symbol renders
因为一个标志总是会渲染 --
always -- it's a vector.
它是一个矢量
You could be inclined to always
你可能会想要
specify this width and height,
指定它的宽度和高度
but it's actually not a good
但这并不是一个好主意
First of all, it's not really
首先 这不是正确的
You can see on the screenshot
你可以看到在屏幕快照上
that the symbol is described as
标志被描述为
a 17-point symbol, which is
17 磅值的标志
really small, but it still
这可以说是非常小
renders as a very large image,
但它还是被视为一个大的图片
because the width and height are
因为宽度和高度
there.
在那摆着
But you can also see that it's
但是你也可以看到
not entirely correctly centered.
它不是完全居中的
Like, it's a little bit off to
它有点偏左 也有点居上
And secondly, it's not
第二 这不是性能 --
performance -- this is not the
这不是展示一个
most performance way to display
标志图像
a symbol image.
最具性能的方法
So what you want to do is not
所以你要做的
constrain the symbol image at
是不压缩标志图像
all, and have it be its natural
并让它保留
size.
原始的大小
In this case, we changed the
在这个例子中 我们把
size of the symbol to 500 points
标志的大小改成了 500 磅
to match the size that we had
以此来匹配
before, and it looks a lot
我们之前的尺寸
better, because it -- the
这样看起来好多了
centering is better than before,
因为它的居中比之前要好
and the size is more correct.
尺寸也正确
This will also be more
性能也更多
So if you do need a fixed size,
如果你需要一个固定的尺寸
set the point size, but
设置磅值大小
otherwise have the symbol react
但是让标志对标志配置
to the symbol configuration,
作出反应
because even a large symbol
因为即便是大的
configuration or a small-scale
标志配置或小型的
configuration may make a big
配置都可能对
difference for the size of the
相同标志的尺寸
same symbol.
带来巨大的改变
Now, there's a lot of
现在 这里有很多配置
configurations here, and we've
我们设定了
established that symbols are --
这些标志 --
Paolo mentioned before that
Paolo 之前提到了
symbols are really made to work
这些标志可以
with San Francisco, our system
与 San Francisco 即我们的系统字体
font, but they work with any
兼容 不过它们可以与任何字体兼容
So you can use this API,
所以你可以使用这个 API
SymbolConfiguration(font, to
SymbolConfiguration(font
create a configuration that
来创造一个可以
matches the font you give it,
与你提供的字体相匹配
and it works with system fonts.
并与系统字体兼容的配置
It works with dynamic type
它可以使用动态类型
fonts, but it also works with
字体 也可以使用
custom fonts.
自定义字体
And especially for custom fonts,
尤其是对于自定义字体来说
it will create a more
它会创造一个
high-fidelity configuration than
比你通过手动复制
the one you can create manually
字体的数值
by copying the values from the
到你的配置中
font into your configuration.
要更保真的配置
So it's better to use this for
所以最好使用
custom fonts.
自定义字体
And when you already have a
当你已经有了一个文本
piece of text or a label that
或者一个配置好字体的标签
an easy way to create a
那就很容易
configuration that matches that
创造一个与字体相配的配置
And the last thing about
关于配置的最后一件事
configurations is that they are
就是它们是不变的
You can't change them.
你不能改变它们
So what if you do want to change
如果你想要改变它们
them?
怎么办呢
Well, you have to combine them.
那你就得把它们结合起来
There's a method called
有一个方法叫
applying, and it applies the
应用 它可以把
specified configuration to the
指定的配置应用至
one that you're calling it on.
你调用的配置上
So we'll take the configuration
我们会采用这个
you're calling it on, and then
你请求的配置
take all the specified values in
然后把所有特定的数值
the other configuration, and
运用到其他配置中
override, or set them on the
然后覆盖 或者在基本配置中
base configuration.
设定它们
And you get a new configuration
你会得到一个
that you can use somewhere else.
可以在其他地方使用的新的配置
But they are immutable, and the
但是它们是不可改变的
configuration themselves won't
配置本身也不变
Now, let's talk about layout.
接下来让我们谈谈布局
We have this simple comments
在我们的 App 中有一个
section in our app, and we want
简单的评论部分
to expand a little bit for our
我们想要在下一个版本中
next version, and also start
扩展这个部分
using symbols here.
同时也开始用标志
And we have this avatar
我们在这里有头像的
placeholder.
占位符
I'm going to focus on just one
我现在要把注意力集中在
row, and Paolo suggested
一行上 Paolo 建议
switching to a new symbol.
换成一个新的标志
So let's try that.
那么让我们试试看
That looks a lot better.
这看起来好多了
So normally, if you would align
一般来说 如果你想把图片
images with a piece of text, you
与文本对齐
would use center alignment --
你可以使用居中对齐
vertical center alignment, and
垂直居中对齐
in most cases, that would look
在大部分情况下
like you would expect, and it
它都会变成你预期的样子
would be the easiest.
这是最简单不过的了
Now, for symbols, there's
标志其实
actually no difference.
也是如此
You can still use vertical
你还是可以使用
center alignments, and it's
垂直居中对齐
actually preferred.
这实际上是首选的
UIKit will actually take the
UIKit 其实也把
typographic information in the
排版信息运用到
symbol and use it to properly
标志中同时使用它让
visually align the symbol versus
标志和文本在
the piece of text, and that
视觉上对齐
might actually happen that the
有时候两个元素的
frames of the two elements are
框架可能并不会相匹配
So the center is optically and
所以这个居中是视觉上的
not absolute, but you don't have
而不是绝对的 但是你
to do anything.
不需要做任何事
The system does it for you.
系统会帮助你
There's, of course, also cases
当然了 标签
where labels have more than one
可能有时候会不止一行
line, and vertical centering
这时候垂直居中
works great here, too.
也能起到很好的作用
Same for symbols, we'll still
标志也是一样
use the typographical
我们还是会使用排版信息
information to properly align
来适当地对齐
for the center of the label.
标签的中间
This is great for disclosure
对于公开指示器
indicators, for example.
来说也很好
And looking back at our view,
我们重新来看看这个画面
the disclosure indicator sits at
指示器就在
the right place where I want it,
我所希望的地方
but I actually want that avatar
但我其实想要
placeholder to be next to my
头像占位符靠近我的第一行
So let's move it.
所以我们来移动一下
In this case, you can use
在这个情况下 你可以使用
baseline alignment, and up until
基线对齐 到现在为止
now, it would be a bit hard to
这可能有点
make this happen.
难以实现
You could do edge alignment,
你也可以选择边缘对齐
because you know the text and
因为你知道文本和标签
the label would be there, or you
会出现在那里
could do baseline alignment, but
或者你也可以选择基线对齐
have to calculate offsets, so it
不过你必须算一算它的偏移
would be weird.
所以这也很奇怪
And in this case, for symbols,
在这种情况下 针对标志
we can just baseline align, and
我们只需要基线对齐
that's it.
就可以了
Thank you.
谢谢
[ Applause ]
[掌声]
And you can actually inspect
实际上你可以检测
this baseline because we
基线 因为我们
introduced a new property on UI
在 UI Image 中引用了一个
Image called
名为 baselineOffsetFromBottom 的
baselineOffsetFromBottom, and it
新性能 它会展示
expresses, like it says, the
正如它所说的
offset to the baseline from the
从图像底部到基线的
bottom of the image.
偏移量数
And it's an optional CG float.
这是一个可选的 CG 浮动
Why? Because not all images have
为什么呢 因为不是所有的图像
baselines.
都有基线
Symbols come with one by
标志在默认情况下有基线
default, but other images don't
但是其他的图像并没有
So you have to check if the
所以你需要检查
image has a baseline in order to
图像是否拥有基线
see if you can use it.
来看你能不能使用它
In Objective-C, there's a
在 Objective-C 中
separate method for it,
针对这个有另外的方法
because they don't have
因为它们并不是可选的
Now, these baselines might be --
这些基线可能
have unexpected values.
有意想不到的值
In this case, we have two symbol
在这种情况下 我们有两个
images.
标志图像
They're right next to a piece of
它们与文本相邻
text.
它们大小相同
they share the same baseline.
拥有相同的基线
But if we visualize their
但如果我们展示出
bounds, you can see that the
它们的范围
chevron is sitting high above
我们会看到这个 v 形图案
the baseline, and the cloud sits
比基线要高很多 而云朵则
over the baseline.
正坐在基线上
And looking at their values, you
如果我们看一眼它们的数值
can see that expressing the
就会发现与底部的
offset from the bottom means
偏移量意味着
that going up is a positive
向上是正数偏移量
offset and going down is a
向下则是
negative offset.
负数偏移量
It also means that it's valid
这也意味着
for an image to have a baseline
它对于一个
that is outside of its bounds,
基线在其范围外的图像是有效的
in this case, the chevron.
比如这个例子中的 v 型图像
And if you have a baseline value
如果你有一个
of zero, it doesn't mean that
基线数值为零
you don't have a baseline.
这并不代表你没有基线
It means that the baseline is
这代表基线
the same as the bottom of the
和图像的底部
image.
是持平的
It's a bit surprising, but it
这听起来很让人吃惊
works.
但却有效
Now, the good thing is, we also
好消息是我们也
added API to add baselines to
增加了 API 可以为图像
images.
增加基线
You would use
你可以使用
withBaselineOffsetFromBottom,
withBaselineOffsetFromBottom
and you would get a new image
然后你就可以得到一个
that has a baseline configured
你请求的
like you asked for.
有基线配置的新的图像
Again, this is an offset in
再次 这是屏幕中的
screen points from the bottom of
离图像底部的偏移量
Now, the nice thing is, the
好消息就是
image will start behaving like a
图像会和标志一样表现
symbol.
这不是一个标志
behave like a symbol, because it
但却会表现得像一个标志
has some typographical
因为它拥有一些
information.
排版信息
And so, you can use the same
所以你可以为标志图像
layout for symbol images as for
使用和普通图像一样的布局
You don't have to check does
你不需要检查
this image have a baseline?
这个图像是否有基线
Then I use this layout, or the
然后我使用这个布局
other way around, and this makes
或者另外一个
that a lot easier.
这一切都更简单了
And looking at our example, we
看看我们的例子
now have actual avatars, and
现在我们可以展示真实的头像
some rows without avatars, and
有些行则没有头像
it looks much better.
这看起来好多了
And I only had to do baseline
我只需要将
alignment for this first line.
第一行基线对齐
It's really easy.
这真的很简单
I also want to touch briefly on
我也想简单谈谈
horizontal alignments.
平行对齐问题
You can see that the images are
你可以看到
horizontally aligned on the same
图像在相同的纵列中
column, and you do this by
是平行对齐的
specifying an offset that you
你可以通过指定一个
want to align to, and then
你想对齐的偏移量
center the images on that
然后把图像放在偏移量中间
offset.
来实现这一点
It's pretty easy.
这很简单
And then you can go from that
然后你可以从偏移量到
offset to the text, or from the
文本 或者从
edge to the text.
边缘到文本
So you should actually center
你实际上应该
align, even horizontally, the
居中对齐 甚至平行对齐图像
images instead of applying a
而不是应用
leading or a trailing constraint
前置或后续的限制
Now, let's go back to our spec.
现在让我们回头看看我们的规范
What I wanted to say is that,
在这里我想说的是
like, by default, it's probably
在默认条件下
a good idea to start with center
初始情况选择中心对齐
alignment, both horizontally and
不论是平行还是垂直
vertically.
都是个好主意
In most cases, that's what you
在大部分情况中
want, and the system will handle
这就是你想要的
everything for you.
系统也会为你处理一切事情
It will use typographical
如果可行的话
information if it's available,
它会使用排版信息
and otherwise, it will use the
不然它就会使用
old-style just centering.
旧式的对齐方式
And in this case, Paolo
在这种情况下
specified baseline alignment,
Paolo 指定了基线对齐
because the second line -- the
因为第二行 --
second item has two lines.
第二个项目有两行
So we'd need to use the
所以我们需要
baseline.
使用基线
Then we can fall back to
然后我们可以回到
baseline alignment, but that's
基线对齐 但是
also very easy.
这也非常简单
And this spec also properly
这个规范也恰当地
specifies horizontal alignment
指定了图像的
of the images.
平行对齐
It makes the spec a lot easier
这使得规范
to read.
易于阅读
Now, let's go back to buttons.
现在让我们来看一下按钮
Buttons -- there's a lot of
按钮 --- 在 UIKit 中
buttons in UIKit.
有很多按钮
We have two types of buttons,
我们有两种类型的按钮
system buttons and regular
系统按钮和
buttons.
常规按钮
Let's start with the system
让我们先从系统按钮开始
First of all, all buttons in
首先 UIKit 里的所有
UIKit come with a preset symbol
按钮都有一个预设的
configuration, and for system
标志配置 对于系统按钮来说
buttons, it's body large.
它的主体是大号的
That means that it reacts to
这意味着它会
dynamic type changes, has a body
根据动态类型的变化进行反应
text style, and a large scale.
有着正文文本风格 和大的尺寸
Now, wouldn't it be great if you
你们不觉得如果你不仅可以创造
could create system buttons,
在 Wi-Fi 网络列表的
like the info button in the
信息按钮
available Wi-Fi networks list,
还可以使用你自己的标志图像
but to create your own system
创建和长相它一样的
buttons that looked exactly the
属于你自己的系统按钮
same, with your own symbol
是一件非常好的
image?
事情吗
Well, we thought it was a good
我们认为这是一个很好的主意
idea, and we added some, an
我们增加了一些
initializer on UIButton that
在 UIButton 的初始化程序
allows you to create a system
让你可以创建一个
button with any symbol image.
拥有标志图像的系统按钮
And it will behave like an --
它会表现得像一个 --
like a regular symbol image.
像一个常规的标志图像
[ Applause ]
[掌声]
Now, let's go to regular
现在 让我们来看看
buttons.
常规按钮
In this case, I have a pop-over,
在这个例子中 我有个弹出式窗口
and they're used as actions in
它们在这个视图中
this view.
作为行动使用
And symbols really shine here.
这些标志在这真的大放异彩
They're really in their place.
他们都在恰当的位置
A regular button comes with a
一个常规的按钮
medium-scale preset.
一般会有一个中等大小的预设
Now, having said -- talking
现在我们已经说过 --
about these preset scales, what
关于这些预设大小的事情
if you want to change them?
如果你想改变它们怎么办呢
Well, there's similar API on
在 UIButton 上
UIButton, as on UIImageView,
有和在 UIImageView 上相似的 API
called
它的名字是
PreferredSymbolConfiguration
PreferredSymbolConfiguration forState
That works exactly like the
它和 UIButton
other content accessors on
上的其他内容访问器
UIButton.
工作原理一样
You can set a configuration for
你可以为配置设定为
certain states.
某些状态
And it gives you maximum
它会给你最大化的弹性
flexibility because you can set
因为你可以设置
an image, you can set a
一个图像 你可以设置
configuration, or you can set
一个配置 或两者都设置
both, and it will work
它也会运行得很好
Another button example is this
另一个按钮的例子就是这个
It kind of shows what we mean
它某种程度上展现了
with symbols and text really
我们所认为的
shine together, but it doesn't
标志与文本完美融合
mean that they're always close
这并不意味着它们经常紧挨着
These two buttons really belong
这两个按钮应该在一起
together, and they're configured
它们的配置
in the same way, both the left
是相同的 不论是左边的按钮
button and the right button.
还是右边的按钮
The preferred symbol
优先加载的标志配置
configuration is matched with
与右边按钮的字体
the font of that right button,
是相配的
and the only difference between
两者唯一的区别是
the two is that the left one has
左边的按钮有一个标志
a symbol, and the right one has
右边的按钮
a piece of text.
有一个文本
And you can see that they share
你可以看到它们的
the same baseline, and because
基线是一样的
their configuration is exactly
因为它们的配置是完全相同的
the same, they also share the
它们也有相同的
same metrics, and it makes
度量标准
layout a lot easier.
这让布局更加简单
And to round off our button
为了完成我们的
story -- I mentioned there's a
按钮工作 -- 我提到过
lot of buttons in UIKit.
在 UIKit 上有很多按钮
We'll go to bar buttons.
我们可以看看状态栏按钮
We have updated all the artwork
我们更新了
in UIKit to use symbols.
UIKit 中的原图以使用标志
It not only applies to bar
它不仅可以运用在
buttons, but everywhere, and bar
状态栏按钮中 还可以运用在任何地方
buttons feel right in place with
状态栏按钮与这些新的原图
the new artwork.
完美契合
Now, if you do back-deploy to
现在 如果你要退回到
older systems, you have to keep
之前的系统
in mind that if you create
你需要记住
custom artwork, on older
如果你在旧系统中
systems, you still get the
创建了自定义原图
previous, thinner artwork than
与新的更新的原图相比
the new, updated artwork.
你会得到之前的更细的原图
So keep that in mind if you
所以请记住
create assets for your
如果你为旧的版本
back-deployment.
创建了素材
You can use symbols in bar
你可以使用带图像的
buttons with images.
状态栏按钮的标志
We have existing API for this,
针对此我们有现成的 API
and you just put a symbol in
你只需要放一个标志
there.
在那就行
And it will feel right in place
它将与系统按钮
with the system buttons.
完美契合
You don't have to do anything
你不需要做任何事
That's all you have to do.
这就是所有你需要做的事情
And again, like regular buttons,
再一次 像常规按钮一样
bar buttons come with the preset
状态栏按钮也有
configuration.
预设好的配置
And in any non-compact size
在任何不压缩的尺寸类中
class, like in portrait mode on
比如你手机中的
your phone, the configuration
人像模式
will be large.
配置都会很大
If you then rotate your phone,
如果你旋转你的手机
and end up in a compact size
最后到了一个压缩尺寸类
class, we will change that
我们会把按钮上的配置
configuration on the button to
改成中等
And this will call the symbol to
这会将标志调用得
slightly be smaller, and to fit
更小 也可以
perfectly in the more compact
完美地契合更压缩的
bars.
状态栏
It also means that you don't
这也意味着
have to provide a secondary
你不再需要提供一个
image anymore, because the
二级图片
system does all the work.
因为系统会帮你完成一切工作
It will scale using the built-in
它会缩放来使用
symbol scales.
内置的标志缩放比例
[ Applause ]
[掌声]
And on the iPad, we're -- we
在 iPad 上 我们 --
always have a large, because of
因为我之前提到过的事情
the things I mentioned before.
我们经常会有一个大尺寸的
Now, another thing about symbols
现在关于标志的另一个东西
is rendering modes.
就是渲染模式
Any regular image has, like,
任何常规图像
color data built into it, but
都有比如颜色数据的导入
for a symbol, it's different.
但是对于标志来说 这是不一样的
It has an intrinsic mode.
它有一个固有的模式
It doesn't have an intrinsic
它没有一个固有的颜色
color.
我们使用 tintColor
render the symbol, and if we
来渲染标志
don't have a tint color, we'll
如果我们没有 tintColor
use black.
那就使用黑色
But don't rely on that black,
但是不要依赖于黑色
because it don't want -- work
因为它不想 --
nice with dark mode, and it
与深色模式融合得很好
might be subject to change.
它可能有改变的倾向
How does this work?
它如何运行呢
The rendering mode on any image
任何图像的渲染模式
is automatic, and up until now,
都是自动的 到现在为止
for any image, that would
对任何图像来说
usually resolve to always
它们都经常偏向
original.
始终绘制原始状态
Now, in -- with symbols, that
现在 对标志来说
changes.
情况不同了
Non-symbol images still usually
非标志图像
resolve to always original, but
还是倾向始终绘制原始状态
symbol images will resolve to
标志图像则会偏向
always template.
始终根据 tintColor 绘制图像
And that means that we'll use
这意味着我们会
the tint color to give them a
使用 tintColor 来为他们上色
color, and that's all there is
事情就是如此
You can change the rendering
你可以通过现有的 API
mode on an image with the
来改变一个图片的
existing API.
渲染模式
Now, I've covered the basic
我们已经讲到了
UIKit controls, but sometimes,
基本的 UIKit 控制
you do want to draw an image in
但有时候你可能会想
a graphic context.
在一个图形环境中绘制图像
And you would probably use
这个时候你可能会用到
draw(in Rect.
draw(in Rect
Now, for symbols, like I
那么 对于标志来说
mentioned before, that's
正如我之前提到的
probably not a good idea,
这可能不是一个好主意
because they want to be their
因为它们想要保留
natural size.
原始的尺寸
So it's better to use draw(at
所以这里最好使用 draw(at
and have the image decide how
让图像决定
large it wants to be.
它想要多大的尺寸
But we have a problem.
但是我们有一个问题
We have this image, but it's too
我们有一张这样的图片
small.
但是它太小了
By default, images come with an
在默认状态下 图片有一个
unspecified configuration.
未指定的配置
Nothing is specified, and if
我们没有指定任何东西
we're just -- if you have to
如果我们只是 -- 如果你们必须
render it, and we don't find a
渲染 而我们没有找到
specific value, we'll fall back
一个特定的数值
to the system defaults.
我们会回到系统初始状态
And in this case, that ends up
在这种情况下
with a pretty small image.
它最终会是一个非常小的图片
Now, I can create a
现在我可以创建
configuration to make it larger
一个配置让它变得更大
-- 34 points, and a bold weight,
- 34 磅 粗体
and then use new API
然后使用新的 API
withConfiguration to apply that
withConfiguration 将
configuration to the image, and
配置运用在图片上
get a new image with that
然后我们可以获得一个
configuration built in.
嵌入该配置的新图片
Which results in this larger,
我们创造出了这个
slightly more bold teacup, which
更大更粗的茶杯
is exactly what I wanted.
这就是我想要的
Going back to our pop-over,
再回到我们的弹出式窗口
Paolo also asked me to change
Paolo 也让我们
the text here, because symbols
改变那里的文本
feel at home in text.
因为标志在文本中很契合
Can we replace some words with
我们可以用一些词语来替换
symbols?
标志吗
Well, we can, but symbols are
答案是肯定的
typographic in nature, but they
标志本质上是排好版的
are still images.
但它们仍然是图片
So we have to use an attributed
所以我们需要使用
string with an NSTextAttachment.
拥有 NSTextAttachment 的属性字符串
Now, this code will look
现在 这个代码看起来
familiar, but we have a new
有点熟悉了 但是我们
piece of API,
有一个新的 API
NSTextAttachment(image that will
那就是 NSTextAttachment(image
create a text attachment with
它会通过附加的图片
the image attached.
创造一个文本附件
Now, this text attachment is a
现在这个文本附件
bit smarter than the regular
比常规的要更加智能
It knows about symbols, and it
它了解标志
will actually inspect the string
也会检查标志周围的字符串
around the symbol to complete
来尽力完成
the configuration of that symbol
标志的配置
It will look at the font size.
它会查看字体大小
It will look at the font weight,
粗细程度
but it will also look at the
但是同时还有颜色
color, and then the completed
然后一个完整的图片就
image will be drawn.
绘制完成了
[ Applause ]
[掌声]
The old API, or the existing API
旧的 API 或者现有的 API
creating a text attachment and
创建文本附件
then assigning the image still
然后指派的图片
works, but it won't get the
还是可以运行
matching behavior.
但是不会获得相匹配的行为
And of course, you can also use
当然了 你也可以
this new API with any regular
使用拥有常规图形的
image.
新的 API
Paolo also wanted some color
Paolo 在这里还想要一些颜色
Looks better.
看起来更好了
Yeah. And we created some new
是的 我们又创造了一些新的
API to do this.
API 去实现它
You can tint an image now.
你现在可以给一张图片着色了
So withTintColor applies a color
所以 withTintColor 给图片
to the image, and it does so
应用一种颜色 它使用起来
very efficiently.
非常高效
It will only render the color
它只有在需要的时候
when it needs to, and then it
才渲染颜色 然后它
will look at the most efficient
会寻找最有效的方法
way to do this.
来做到这点
And before, you would probably
在此之前 你可能
have to rasterize an image, and
必须对图像进行栅格化 并且
render into a graphics context,
并将它渲染到图形上下文中
and then apply a color.
然后再应用颜色
You don't have to do that
你再也不需要
anymore.
这么做了
This takes care of this.
这样就搞定了
[ Applause ]
[掌声]
And it's especially important
这对于标志来说
for symbols, because they don't
格外重要 因为它们没有
have an intrinsic color, and
一个固定的颜色
this will give them a color.
这就给了它们一个颜色
Now, symbols also have a
现在 标志也有了
different rendering mode.
不同的渲染模式
So if you really want that color
所以如果你真的想要让那种颜色
to pop out, you have to change
弹出 你必须改变
the rendering mode, and you can
渲染模式 你可以
do it in one go with this
使用这个可选参数
optional parameter.
一次性完成
Now, these two APIs are not in
现在 这两个 API 还没有包含在
the first beta, but they will
第一个 beta 版里  但是它们
come soon.
很快就会被包含
So we've seen a lot of API, and
所以我们已经看过了很多 API
we think we provided you with a
我们认为我们提供了一个
great tool set to make your apps
很棒的工具组可以让你们的 App
really shine in iOS 13.
在 iOS 13 中大放异彩
But there's a few tips.
但是 这里有几个建议
Prefer horizontal and vertical
与边缘对齐相比
centering over edge alignment.
应更倾向于水平和垂直居中
It's a bit of a mental shift,
它是一个思路上的转变
but once you figure it out, it
但是一旦你弄明白了
really works out.
它就会真的奏效
And try to build your layouts
试着从最小元素到
from the smallest element up to
最大元素
the largest element.
构建你的布局
It's pretty easy to start with
从一些小东西开始
something small and then use it
然后把它们当成一块积木
as a building block to make
去做成更大的东西
something larger.
这是非常容易
And be flexible.
并且灵活的
Image sizes can change.
图像大小可以改变
Allow your image views to be the
这就允许你的图像视图
size of their image but be aware
和他们的图像尺寸相同  但是注意
of the fact that they can
它们是可以更改的
It can be at run time, or it can
它可能发生在运行时 或者
be over app launches, or even
App 启动时 又甚至
over system updates.
是系统更新时
Caching images usually doesn't
缓存图像通常
help.
没有什么用
It's a great source of bugs, and
它是 Bug 的一大来源
the system already does its best
系统已经竭尽所能地
to provide the best performance
提供了最好的性能
And caching really gives you an
并且缓存真的会
override, so there's no need to
覆盖 所以没必要那样做
And finally, rasterizing is, in
最后 栅格化
most cases, the worst solution,
在大多数情况下 是最坏的解决方案
or the least-optimal solution to
起码不是修复问题的
fix the problem.
最佳解决方案
So save your CPU cycles for
所以节省你的 CPU 资源
something useful, and let the
来做些有用的事情
system rasterize an image.
让系统栅格化图像吧
So try to avoid rasterizing
尽量避免栅格化
images, especially symbol
图像 特别是
images.
标志图像
The accessibility and
今天上午的
localization sessions this
可访问性和本地化会议
morning were -- are very
非常有趣
because symbols make adaptation
因为标志使这些领域的适配
in those areas a lot simpler.
变得简单得多
And there's the Implementing
明天将会推出
Dark Mode tomorrow, where
深色模式 该模式下
symbols also really shine
标志会因为暗色调
because of dark tint color.
而非常闪耀
There are two labs you might be
这还有两个实验室你可能
interested in.
会感兴趣
There's a text and SF symbols
在周四有文本和 SF symbols 实验室
lab, and fonts lab on Thursday,
以及字体实验室
and there's a design lab on
在周五下午
Friday afternoon.
还有一个设计实验室
And of course, you're welcome at
当然 任何 UIKit 实验室都
any of the UIKit labs.
欢迎你们
Thank you so much for listening
非常感谢你的聆听
and enjoy the rest of your WWDC.
享受接下来的 WWDC 大会吧
[ Applause ]
[掌声]